Preliminary Inventory to the Metropolitan Council on Housing Records TAM.173
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series IV: 2008 Accession., 8.0 linear feet
  - Landlords and Developers West Side, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Landlords Organization v. Rent Control Stabilization Laws, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Lehman, Franz, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Lincoln Center Tower Square, 1977-1994 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Logue, Edward, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Lopez, Margacita, 1997-1998 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Messinger, Ruth, undated (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - New Alliance Party (I), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - New Alliance Party (II), 1982 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Political Action Committee, 1994-2003 (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - Queens, Flushing, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 44)
  - Queens, General, 1967-1991 (Box 64, Folder 45)
  - Queens, Jamaica, 1962-1963 (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - Rehabilitation, 1974-1977 (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - Rent Regulation Reform, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - Rent Stabilization Association, 1991-1994 (Box 64, Folder 49)
  - Runyon, Marie, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 50)
  - Schechter, Howard, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 51)
  - Scott, Walter, undated (Box 64, Folder 52)
  - Starr, Roger, 1970-1985 (Box 64, Folder 53)
  - Stringer, Scott, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 54)
  - Tucker, William, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 55)
  - Vallone, Peter, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 56)
  - Velella, Guy, undated (Box 64, Folder 57)
  - ACORN, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Action Council of Tenants for Yonkers, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Action for Community Empowerment, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Adopt a Building, 1970-1978 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Albany, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Asian Americans for Equality, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Battery Park City, 1963-1978 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Chelsea, 1978-1992 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Coalition Against Rent Increase, 1982-2005 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Coalition to Save Lincoln Center Home for Senior Citizens, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Convention Center, 1973-1977 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Co-op City, 1965-1976 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Co-op City, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Co-op/Condo Conversion, 1975-1991 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1962-1995 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - East Harlem, 1984-1989 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Ebbets Field Tenants Action Council, 1964-1986 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act (I), 1974-1989 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act (II), 1974-1984 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1962-1968 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Glen Oaks Tenants Associations, 1981-1986 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Housing Policy, 1961-1971 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Lower East Side, 1982-2001 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Lower East Side Joint Planning Council, 1982-1986 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Lower Manhattan Expressway, 1962-1963 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Mandatory Rent Deposit, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Manhattan Valley Spanish Civic Organization, 1964-1966 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Rent Controlled Equalized Assessed Valuation, 1969-1974 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Rent Control Exemptions for Elderly, 1973-1979 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Rent Control New York State Committee Living Costs and The Economy, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Rent Control Outside New York City (I), 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Rent Control Outside New York City (II), 1978-1979 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Rent Control Outisde New York City (III), 1975-1988 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Rent Control Outside New York City (IV), 1973-1979 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Rent Controls (I), 1978-1989 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Rent Controls (II), 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Rent Guidelines, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Rent Regulations, 1987-2002 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1982-1997 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Rent Stabilization Clippings, 1968-2002 (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Rent Stabilization Westchester, 1975-1997 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Seward Park Extension, 1968-1988 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Tax Prop, 1975-1981 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - Two Bridges, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - West Side Housing Forum, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - West Village, 1963-1975 (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - 7-A, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Abandonment, 1969-1994 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Arson, 1978-1982 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Artists Housing, 1964-1988 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Benedict, Jane, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Boerum Hill, 1966-1976 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Brighton Beach, 1966-1974 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Bronx Crisis Coalition, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Brooke Amendment, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Brooklyn Bridge, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Equal, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Brownsville, 1961-1969 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Coney Island, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - East New York, 1965-1989 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Flatbush, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Fort Greene, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Harlem, undated (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Infestation/Mold, 2000-2003 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Met Council Internal, 1966-2003 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Fliers, 1972-2002 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Reports/Newsletters, undated (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Tenants Associations, 1997-2007 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Mitchell-Lama, 1984-2003 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - New York Is Our Home, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Northside Brooklyn (Williamsburg, Greenpoint), undated (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Paerdegat Basin, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Park Slope, 1975-1985 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Parkway-Stuyvesant-Community Life, 1961-1966 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Rent Control Canada, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Rent Stabilization (Early Years), 1969-1978 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Security, 1985-1987 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Security Deposit, 1968-1978 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - Senior Housing, 1970-2003 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Senior Housing, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Sheepshead Bay Focus Public Housing Abandonment, 1965-1966 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - South Bronx, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - SRO, 1989-1991 (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - SRO, 1970-2001 (Box 66, Folder 39)
  - Subleasing, 1983-1986 (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - Succession Rights, 1985-1992 (Box 66, Folder 41)
  - Tenants and Neighbors, 1995-2003 (Box 66, Folder 42)
  - Vacancy Decontrol, 1971-1987 (Box 66, Folder 43)
  - Welfare, 1978-1985 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Where the Money Can Come From, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Where They Come From, Where They Go, 1973-1977 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Window Gates/Guards, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Zoning, 1970-1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Assoication of Neighborhood Housing Developers, 1982-1988 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Budger and code Enforcement, 1993-1998 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - City Planning, 1960-1966 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Code Enforcement, 1968-1969 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Code Enforcement, 1971-1978 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Code Enforcement, 1976-1990 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Con Edison, 1974-1976 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Con Edison, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Con Edison, 1977-1979 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1970-1975 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1981-1982 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Co-op Conversion (I), 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Co-op Conversion (II), 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Co-op/Condo, 1987-1989 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Emergency Repair Program, 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Gay Rights, 1971-1989 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Gentrification, 1980-1999 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Harassment, 1970-1997 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Hardship, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Heat, 1980-1984 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Heat, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Homelessness in New York City, 1982-1989 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Hospital Expansion, 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Hot Water, 1979-1985 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Hotels, 1982-1986 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Hotels, 1983-1985 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Lead, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Lead, 1999-2000 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Lead Legislation Letters, 1998-2004 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Lead Paint, 1983-1994 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Lead Paint, 1996-1998 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Lead Paint, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Lead Paint, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Lead Paint, 2000-2003 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Major Capital Improvements, 1980-1988 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Major Capital Improvements, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Major Capital Improvements, 1989-1992 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Major Capital Improvements (I), 1990 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Major Capital Improvements (II), 1990 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - 8A Loan, 1980-1987 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Bellevue, 1964-1967 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn Arms, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Commodore Hotel, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Displacement, 1988-2001 (Box 68, Folder 12, Box 69)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1973-1984 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1990-1992 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal (I), 1991-1992 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal (II), 1991-1992 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, undated (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 2000-2003 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Drugs, 1987-1991 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Drugs, 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Dry Cleaners, 1993-1997 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Economics of Real Estate, 1974-1983 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Foreclosure, 1973-1992 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Freddie Mac, 1988-1992 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Garden Apartments, 1979-1986 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1968-1982 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1977-1979 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Housing Initiative, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Incinerators, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - Intercoms, Bells, Buzzers, 1967-1968 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Koch, Ed, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Koch, Ed, 1981-1984 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - National People's Action, 1975-1982 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - Network Magazine, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - People's Firehouse, 1982-1987 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - Planners for Equal Opportunity, 1967-1971 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Redlining, 1962-1977 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Redlining, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Redlining, 1977-1979 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Rent Laws, 1993-1999 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1993-1994 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Settlement Housing Fund, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Tenants Rights, 1973-1975 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Union of City Tenants, 1985-1988 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Series V: Audio
  The majority of the materials in this series are recordings of Jane Benedict's radio program "Tenants Fight For Survival," which was broadcast on WBLS.
  Related Archival Materials
  Metropolitan Council on Housing audio materials that came to the repository between 2002 and 2007 can be found in Series III, box 27.
  - Jane Benedict and Curti Truehart with Helen Cousin: Crown Heights (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero: Redemption Bill and Tenant Control (Side 2)., Jan 14, 1978 & Jan 24; 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Ruth Steele: Mitchell-Lama Housing (Side 2)., Aug 6, 1978 & Aug, 13 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Major Owens WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict, Juanita Nesbit, and Bess Stevenson on "In rem" and HPD. (Side 2)., Aug 20, 1978 & Aug 8, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict, Bess Stevenson, and Mrs. Ootine WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Assemblyman Frank Barbaro WBLS (Side 2)., Sep 3, 1978 & Sep 10, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Robert Marerro WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict with PKH on HPD: The Only Solution (Side 2)., Sep 17, 1978 & Sep 24, 1978 (Box 70)
  - WNYC: Special Report Guest Peter Hawley- Housing in the Public Domain, Sep 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Peter K. Hawley (Part II): HPD (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart WBLS (Side 2)., Oct 1, 1978 & Oct 8, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict, Joe Hyler, Mrs. Gigliotti - re: 3681 Broadway WBLS (Side 1). Tom Granger and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 2)., Oct 15, 1978 & Oct 22 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Bendict, Mrs. Ghigliotti, Camacho; and Joe Hyler WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Tome Grainger (RENA) WBLS (Side 2)., Oct 15, 1978 & Oct 22, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart: Quincy Street, Crown Heights (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson WBLS (Side 2)., Nov 5, 1978 & Nov 12, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict, Andy Tate, and Cooper: LeFrack City [not a good recording] (Side 1). Jane Benedict and PKH: HDP Subsidized Housing, Mitchell-Lama, Manhattan Plaza (Side 2)., Nov 19, 1978 & Nov 26, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Bob Marerro WBLS; Dec 9 Conference and Brooklyn Court (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart: Arson (Side 2)., Dec 3, 1978 & Dec 10, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson: Settlement Housing Fund (Side 1). Jane Benedict solo WBLS (Side 2)., Dec 17, 1978 & Dec 24, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Bob Marerro: In rem etc. Part I (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Bob Marerro: In rem Part II (Side 2)., Dec 31, 1978 & Jan 7, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Bendict and Miriam Friedlander: In rem (Side 1). Jane Benedict, Bob Marrero, and Katie Nichson: 2 Party checks, etc. (Side 2), Jan 28, 1979 & Feb 11, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict,Tom Grainger, and Mrs. Ghigliotti, Feb 2, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict (Solo) WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Major Owens WBLS (Side 2)., Feb 18, 1979 & Feb 25, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Katy Nichson WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict WBLS: Rent Controls and Legislation, Mar 4, 1979 & Mar 11, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero: Rent Control Hearings WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and William Moses of CHIP: "Let's Find Out" (Side 2)., Mar 18, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson- Rent Increases (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Robert Macrero- "Re in Rem" (Side 2)., Mar 25, 1979 & Apr 1, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Reverend Timothy Mitchell (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Chas Rangel (Side 2)., April 8, 1979 & April 22, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: How you can fight rising rents with Jane Benedict, Apr 15, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict, Apr 29, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict, May 6, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict with Lloyd Morris and Curtis Trueheart., May 13, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict-WBLS Labor Cost Repeal; Flynn-Dearie's Rent Guidelines (Side 1). Tenant Fight for Survival with guest Congressman Ted Weiss and Eng. Pat Johnon (Side 2)., May 27, 1979 & Jun 3, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero for WBLS re: Rent Guidelines (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero for WBLS re: Park West Village Victory and Warranty of Habitability (Side 2)., June 24, 1979 & Jul 1, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict with Arlene Francis WOR-AM, Jun 26, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson Parts 1 and 2., Jul 22, 1979 & Jul 29, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival; Jane Benedict and Bob Marrerro re: In Rem Before Board of Estimate (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Robert Marrero WBLS on Rent Increases (Side 2)., Aug 12, 1979 - Aug 19, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson on Heat, Organizing, and Hearing, Aug 21, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict-WBLS (Side 1). Met Council Jim Haughton and Jane Benedict (Side 2)., Aug 27, 1979 & Sep 2, 1979 (Box 70)
  - WBLS Jane Benedict and Thomas Granges on In Row Houses (Side 1).Jane Benedict WBLS and Wilhemina Banks (Open Housing Center) (Side 2)., Sep 9, 1979 & Sep 16, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and William Moses of Community Housing Improvement Program (CHIP) WHN/Susan Dempsy "In the Public Interest" (Side 1)/ Jane Benedict and Robert Marrero WBLS- On Various Rent Hearings., Sep 16, 1979 & Sep 23, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict with LeFrak City representatives Richard Isles and David Washington (Side 1). Bob Marrero and Jane Benedict WBLS- Hearings and Tenant Unity Day (Side 2)., Sep 30, 1979 & Oct 7, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict on Tenant Unity Day etc. (Side 1). Nat Shapiro, Marty Bierbaum, Peter Hawlery on "Tenant Management" (Side 2)., Oct 14, 1979 & Oct 19, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict-WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Curtis Trueheart-WBLS (Side 2)., Oct 28,1979 & Nov 4, 1979 (Box 70)
  - WBLS 7AM-with Curtis Trueheart: Chevra Foundation (Side 1). Bob Marrero WBLS- Abandoned Housing (Side 2)., Nov 11, 1979 & Nov 18, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Apartment Living- WFDU-FM 98.1 Nat Shapiro and Pete K. Hawley, Nov 12, 1979 & Nov 23, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight #1: Jane Benedict and Bob Marerro- Don't Freeze (Side 1). Tenants Fight #2: Jane Benedict - Rents and Rent Guidelines (Side 2)., Dec 16, 1979 & Dec 23, 1979 (Box 70)
  - WBLS Jane Benedict and Nancy Biberman of MFY Legal Services- Rent Strike, Nov 25, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight #3, Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart - re: Crown Heights (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart - re: Section 236 rebates through HUD (Side 2)., Dec 30, 1979 & Jan 6, 1980 (Box 70)
  - WBLS Jane Benedict, Jan 13, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Tom Grauper and Jane Benedict - In rem Progress (Side 1). WBLS Tenants Survival: Willa Cummings (Bx. Baruch) and Jane Benedict (Side 2)., Jan 20, 1980 & Feb 10, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenant Fight: Bob Marrero and Jane Benedict - Fuel Cost Passalong (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival Bob Marrero and Jane Benedict - Fuel Cost Passalong and Oil Costs (Side 2)., Jan 27, 1980 & Feb 3, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict and Tom Granger - re: In rem to 495ft.; WBLS Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart from 495ft. (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Burtis Trueheart and Committee of Brooklyn Avenue; Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero (Side 2)., Mar 9, 1980-Mar 30, 1980 (Box 70)
  - WBLS Katie Nichson (Harlem B.) and Jane Benedict, Mar 16, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Bess Stevenson and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival, Guest Bob Marrero (Side 2)., Apr 27, 1980 & Jul 6, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Bess Stevenson and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival- Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero, Apr 27, 1980 & Jul 6, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Phillis Spiro - Open Housing Center and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 1). Curtis Truehart and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 2)., May 6, 1980 & June 29, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict and James Haughton (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict and Richard James (Side 2)., Jun 8, 1980 & Jun 22, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Richard James (Grilevell Tenant Association) and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 1), June 15, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival: Bess Stevenson and Bob Marrero - Fuel Passalong-leases (Side 2)., Jul 13, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: guest Curtis Trueheart (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival: guest Tom Granger (Side 2)., Jul 20, 1980 & Jul Tenants Fight for Survival: guest Curtis Trueheart (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival: guest Tom Granger (Side 2). 27, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: guest Curtis Trueheart (Side 1). Tenants Fight For Survival: guest Curtis Trueheart (Side 2)., Aug 3, 1980 & Aug 17, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Guest Aurea Rodroquez (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival: with Claudia Mausbeck and Jane Benedict., Aug 10, 1980 & Sep 7, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival (Side 1). Tenants Fight For Survival: Bob Marrero and Jane Benedict (Side 2)., Aug 24, 1980 & Sep 14, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival (Side 2)., Sep 16, 1980 & Sep 28 1980 (Box 70)
  - Wins News Conference- Jane Benedict, Maurice Paprin, and John Dearie (Side 1), Sep 28, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Jane Benedict "Tenant Survival" with Thomas Granger (Side 1). Jane Benedict- Legislative Wrap-up (Side 2)., Oct 12, 1980 & Oct 19, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Ray Wallace and Jane Benedict on Carnegie Hall Tenants (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival (Chelsea): Anna Cruz, Jane Wood, and Jane Benedict: West 15 Street Building (Side 2)., Nov 2, 1980-Nov, 30, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: guest Bess Stevenson (Side 1).Tenants Fight for Survival: guest Ida Pollack (Side 2)., Dec 28, 1980 & Jan 4, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Phyllis Spiro - Open Housing Center (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival: Review of Heat Crisis, Jane Benedict (Side 2)., Jan 11, 1981 & Jan 25, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Rent Strike with Curtis Trueheart (Side 1). Jane and Lakeview with Donald Reed (Side 2)., Feb 15, 1981 & Mar 10, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Tenant Survival: Jane Benedict on J51 ER., Feb 22, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Met Council on Housing- 250-54 Park Place (Side 1). Tenants Fight For Survival: Met Council on Housing - Gentrification (Side 2)., Feb 21, 1982 & Feb 7, 1982 (Box 70)
  - "The Tree of Life: A Solution to Inner City Crime, Miseducation & Gentrification" An interview with KANYA founder and director (Side 1). "The Tree of Life: Conclusion", Sep 30, 1982 (Box 70)
  - Tenants Fight, 28:00., Oct 26 (Box 70)
  - WSTU Workshop: Nancy Kyriacou-Background Rent Control. Jos Spencer., undated (Box 70)